#### Contact

dannysnow77@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dannysnow77 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Customer Service SQL Soft Skills

### Certifications

Cisco Introduction to Cyber Security

# **Daniel Effiong**

Frontend Developer - Fellow at TIIDELab/E-learning Trainer Nigeria

## Summary

An enthusiastic individual with 7 years of total experience in roles as Administrative assistant, E-learning Technical Support officer & Operations & Monitoring officer with the capability to work well in a team as well as alone. An aspiring UI developer trained in HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript in UI/UX web applications development. Also an elearner trainer in e-learning solutions.

## Experience

TIIDELab
Frontend Developer - Fellow
July 2021 - Present (2 months)
Federal Capital Territory, Abuja - Nigeria.

Stepcho Group of Companies Ltd.
Operations & Monitoring Logistics Officer.
August 2019 - December 2020 (1 year 5 months)
Abuja

Chips Bits & Bytes Ltd Technical Support March 2016 - November 2018 (2 years 9 months) Abuja.

#### **Duties:**

- # Carry out e-learning Presentations.
- # Installation of e-learning solutions as well as give Technical Support.
- # Carry out trainings/Appraisals, etc.

EchoTech Business Solutions, Utako. Administrative Assistant February 2015 - December 2016 (1 year 11 months) Abuja

### Duties:

# Deputizing in the absence of the management Team

- # Approving time records and requests for time off
- # Making follow-ups with prospective clients via telephone calls.
- # Writing reports for senior management and delivering e-learning presentations.

## Education

Federal Polytechnic Bauchi, Bauchi State.

Higher National Diploma (HND), Computer Science · (February 2007 - October 2012)

Government Secondary School Karu - Abuja, Nigeria. Senior School Certificate · (September 1996 - October 2001)